[
    {
        "question_text":"Which is Isaac's Main in Apex",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Octane",
            "answer_2":"Mad Maggie",
            "answer_3":"Catalyst",
            "answer_4":"Wattson",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },    {
        "question_text":"Which is not a song Isaac can rap all the way through",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Stupid Hoe - Nicki Minaj",
            "answer_2":"Love The Way You Lie - Eminem",
            "answer_3":"Downtown - Macklemore",
            "answer_4":"Work - Iggy Azalea",
            "right_answer":2
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which is not a language Isaac has tried to learn at some point?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Korean",
            "answer_2":"Spanish",
            "answer_3":"French",
            "answer_4":"Norwegian",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What is Isaac's most watched music video",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Hunt",
            "answer_2":"Without You",
            "answer_3":"My Wings",
            "answer_4":"Kick It",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What is the most infuriating thing about Troye Sivan's Rush",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Tush and Rush don't rhyme (not even slant)",
            "answer_2":"A total bottom says hes 'Addicted to your tush'",
            "answer_3":"The song was leaked a month early so i had to wait",
            "answer_4":"The album cover is too sexy, I dont need to be horny",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"When would Isaac be ok touching a sticker",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"When it's on fruit",
            "answer_2":"A Bandaid at the doctor",
            "answer_3":"Taking the doordash sticker off to get the food",
            "answer_4":"None of the Above",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },    {
        "question_text":"Which is Isaac's favorite fake Apple Bottom Jeans cover?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Bad Guy - Billie Eilish",
            "answer_2":"Hit Me Baby One More Time - Britney",
            "answer_3":"My Heart Will Go On - Celine Dion",
            "answer_4":"A Thousand Miles - Vanessa Carlton",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which cartoon show has Isaac seen 4 times through?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"American Dad",
            "answer_2":"Bobs Burgers",
            "answer_3":"South Park",
            "answer_4":"Futurama",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which porn did Isaac beat karen with?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Silicon Penises",
            "answer_2":"Cake Feet Fetish",
            "answer_3":"Cereal in the Ass",
            "answer_4":"Kitten Egg",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Who was the last person here to be between 4 and 5 feet of Isaac's boner",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Daniel",
            "answer_2":"Karen",
            "answer_3":"Aidan",
            "answer_4":"Bradley",
            "right_answer":2
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Who was the last person here Isaac kissed",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Aidan",
            "answer_2":"Holly",
            "answer_3":"Vincent",
            "answer_4":"Bradley",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },    {
        "question_text":"Who has not been Isaac's fav pornstar at a time",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Joey Mills",
            "answer_2":"Johnny Rapid",
            "answer_3":"Felix Fox",
            "answer_4":"Ben Masters",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Isaac has 3 straight porns he considers hot. Which is wrong.",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Family Swaps, then step relatives fuck",
            "answer_2":"Stepbrother Pumpkin, mom vacuums",
            "answer_3":"Vintage Cheerleaders selling tickets",
            "answer_4":"Kacey Jordan has the fattest pussy",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which is not a confirmed Isaac skill name?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Gluck Gluck 3000",
            "answer_2":"Finger Linger 2000",
            "answer_3":"Lick Lick 1000",
            "answer_4":"Slurp Slurp 500",
            "right_answer":2
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which is not a real Isaac hookup story",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Guy came while Karen peed",
            "answer_2":"3 bottoms, 3 hour fuck session no breaks",
            "answer_3":"Isaac Breeds Guy in construction site",
            "answer_4":"Guy gets oral then pukes",
            "right_answer":2
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Who has known Isaac the second longest?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Holly",
            "answer_2":"Bradley",
            "answer_3":"Jake",
            "answer_4":"Vincent",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    }
]